hi spring fans welcome to another
嗨， Spring 粉丝们欢迎来到另一个
installment of spring tips in this video
本视频中的 spring 技巧 分期付款
we're gonna return to the topic of
我们将回到主题
testing in a previous installment we
在上一期的测试中，我们
looked at testing and we covered you
看了测试，我们为您覆盖
know a fairly large contingent of sort
知道相当大的队伍
of the things you might want to use in
您可能想在其中使用的东西
the in the spring ecosystem to test a
在 Spring 生态系统中进行测试
fairly traditional sort of micro-service
相当传统的微服务
e spring boot based applications or
基于Spring Boot的应用程序或
spring cloud if you will based
如果你愿意的话， Spring 的云
applications
应用领域
I started small and then worked our way
我从小开始，然后按照自己的方式工作
up to micro services in this spring tip
在今年 Spring 的微服务中
this follow up spring tip we're gonna do
这个后续的 spring 技巧 ，我们要做
basically the same thing you know same
你知道的基本相同
domain model same everything but we're
域模型的一切都一样，但我们
gonna do so in context of reactive
会在反应性的情况下这样做
programming right when this is this this
这是这个时的正确编程
brings some different challenge that
带来了一些不同的挑战
with challenges that we didn't have to
挑战，而我们不必
really confront when we get when we do
当我们做的时候真正面对
when we tested sort of traditional
当我们测试某种传统
spring MVC servlet based and nonreactive
基于Spring MVC Servlet的非反应式
sort of data access and web endpoints so
这样的数据访问和Web端点
in this video we're gonna do basically
在这部影片中，我们基本上要做
the same thing but do so in the context
同样的事情，但要在上下文中这样做
of reactive programming or through the
反应式编程或通过
lens of reactive programming so as usual
反应性编程的镜头像往常一样
we're gonna start here and start to
我们将从这里开始，并开始
spring that i/o we're going to build a
Spring ，我/我们将建立一个
producer application this is gonna be a
生产者应用程序，这将是一个
thing that serves data and we're gonna
服务数据的东西，我们要
use the latest and greatest to that one
使用最新和最伟大的那个
one snapshot we're gonna create a
我们要创建一个快照
reactive web application that uses
使用的反应式Web应用程序
Lombok and can use the spring cloud
龙目岛，可以用 Spring 的云
contract verifier and it's gonna use it
合同验证程序，它将使用它
reactive MongoDB I've got right I've got
反应性MongoDB我已经正确，我已经正确
my MongoDB running on my local machine
我在本地计算机上运行的MongoDB
at the moment and so we'll just use that
此刻，所以我们将使用它
and I'll go to the console here and open
我将转到此处的控制台并打开
up my producer in my IDE as usual and so
像往常一样在我的IDE中提高我的生产者，等等
what we're gonna do just very very
我们要做的非常非常
simple application is we're gonna drive
简单的应用程序就是我们要开车
this application the development of this
这个应用程序的发展
application by building tests first and
首先通过构建测试来进行应用
the benefit of doing that is that we can
这样做的好处是我们可以
we can as I explained last time take
我们可以像我上次解释的那样
solace knowing that every single test we
安慰，知道我们每一次测试
might result in a result in work that we
可能会导致我们工作的结果
don't have to do it's not a chore that I
不必做，这不是我的琐事
ask that we have to loop back around and
要求我们必须循环回去，
do after we've written the production
写完作品后要做
code it is something that we already by
编码，这是我们已经通过的
virtue of the fact that we've made it
我们已经做到这一点
green have also sort of delivered a
绿色也提供了
feature right each time we make a test
每次测试时功能正确
pass when we write the test first we by
当我们首先编写测试时通过
definition also deliver the
定义还提供了
that we're testing as opposed to
我们正在测试而不是
delivering the future and then going
传递未来，然后走向
back and writing the test which feels a
返回并编写测试，感觉
bit like a chore we're trying to trigger
有点像我们要触发的琐事
ultimately the dopamine you hit you know
最终你击中的多巴胺知道
that euphoria you get from feeling like
从那种感觉中得到的快感
you're making progress quickly so we're
您正在快速进步，所以我们
gonna write a test first we're gonna do
首先要写一个测试，我们要做
so by going to the test package source
因此，请转到测试包源
test resources of course and I'm gonna
当然要测试资源，我要
go to producer application test and this
去生产者应用测试，这个
is a brand-new spring good application
是全新的 Spring 良好应用程序
and it's given us a skeletal test class
这给了我们骨骼测试课
here but we're gonna delete that because
在这里，但我们要删除它，因为
actually that's not a very good test
其实这不是一个很好的测试
it's not how we want to start our
这不是我们想要开始我们的方式
development and our first test is going
开发，我们的第一个测试正在进行
to concern itself with a particular
关心某件事
entity in this case it's gonna be an
在这种情况下，它将是一个实体
entity that writes data to the database
将数据写入数据库的实体
it's gonna be a reservation entity and
这将是一个预订实体，
you know I want to just create a
你知道我只想创建一个
reservation POJO test this is going to
预订POJO测试这将
concern itself with our objects ability
关注自己的目标能力
to have the structures that we expect ok
具有我们期望的结构
so I'm gonna create a standard stock
所以我要创建标准库存
standard J unit test
标准J单元测试
ok so public void you know create ok
好的，所以您知道创建的公共无效
just very simple nothing fancy about
只是非常简单，没有幻想
this at all application and we'll create
在所有应用程序中，我们将创建
a reservation
预约
okay so reservation R equals new
好吧，所以保留R等于new
reservation of course we've got a
保留当然，我们有一个
failing test that is to say it's not
测试失败即不是
compiling and so we need to make it
编译，所以我们需要做
compile so we do that by writing
编译，所以我们通过编写来做到这一点
production code IntelliJ really can
生产代码IntelliJ确实可以
guide us a guidance or a long ways here
在这里指导我们指导或很长一段路
so I've already fixed the sort of you
所以我已经解决了你的那种问题
know so to speak failing test now I want
我现在知道要说失败测试
to UM have a constructor that takes as
到UM有一个构造函数
its first parameter a an ID and a second
它的第一个参数是ID，第二个参数
parameter will be the reservation name
参数将是保留名称
now I could write this code myself but
现在我可以自己编写这段代码，但是
I'm fairly lazy so I'm gonna use Lombok
我很懒，所以我要用龙目岛
line box on the come on the class path
班级路径上的线框
and I'm going to use it to generate
我将用它来生成
through compile time code generation the
通过编译时代码生成
ID field and the reservation name fields
ID字段和预订名称字段
so private string reservation name and I
所以私人字串保留名称和我
don't need the constructor more do I
不需要构造函数更多
write Lombok will do it for me so that
写龙目岛会为我做的
that's the structure of my object and
那就是我的对象的结构，
really at this point all I want to do is
实际上，我现在要做的就是
I want to confirm
我要确认
just as before that you know the basics
就像之前您了解基础知识一样
work so I'm gonna say our docket ID
工作，所以我要说我们的证件号码
equals you know okay which is not a very
等于你知道好吧，这不是很
good we're gonna say is certain no
好，我们要说确定不
actually it's a better test so what I
实际上这是一个更好的测试，所以我
say
说
search know and prove that works good
搜索知道并证明效果很好
and let's see what else want to also use
让我们看看还有什么要用的
the hamcrest matcher so we can say that
hamcrest比赛者，所以我们可以说
our docket reservation name matchers
我们的机票预订名称匹配器
right nothing too reactive about this
对这个没有什么反应
but it does give us a chance to sort of
但这确实给了我们机会
review the basics and of course we can
复习基础知识，我们当然可以
use assertions in certain Jaso
在某些Jaso中使用断言
assertions that are not yet reservation
尚未保留的断言
name and this gives us this nice auto
名称，这给了我们这个不错的汽车
completing fluid you know type sensitive
完成您知道类型敏感的流体
type of where auto-completed option you
自动完成选项的类型
know here so we can say Jane
知道在这里，所以我们可以说简
alright so there's our three test very
好了，所以我们有三个测试
very simple we could just run this code
非常简单，我们可以运行此代码
as written and let's see what we get
就像写的一样，让我们​​看看我们得到了什么
all right seems okay good let's move up
好吧，好吧，我们继续前进
a little bit we know we have a basic
一点点，我们知道我们有一个基本的
POJO you know the structure of the
POJO你知道的结构
object is correct why we can we can
对象是正确的，为什么我们可以
write things to the field and pull them
写东西到田里拉
back out again and and do that very
再次退出，并做到这一点
basic sort of interrogatory poking of
基本的询问性戳
the object but now I want to create an
该对象，但现在我想创建一个
entity that is to say something that we
实体就是说我们
can then persist to MongoDB so I'm gonna
然后可以坚持到MongoDB，所以我要
create a entity a document I suppose in
创建一个我想在其中的文档的实体
this case it's called a document and the
在这种情况下，它称为文档，
MongoDB we rolled say you have a you
我们推出了MongoDB，说你有你
have a a collection which is a table and
有一个表的集合，
in the collection of multiple documents
在收集多个文件中
which are rows in there and table
在那和表中的行
basically so reservation document test
基本上所以预订文件测试
and all we're trying to do here is to
我们在这里要做的就是
confirm that as I write data to the
确认当我将数据写入
database that I can then pull it back
我可以将其拉回数据库
out again you know with its integrity
再次知道你的完整性
right and with all of us and solved with
正确并与我们所有人一起解决
all this pieces still the way we connect
所有这些仍然是我们联系的方式
them to me so persist throws exception
他们给我，所以坚持抛出异常
and I'm gonna write this data to the
我要把这些数据写到
database here now I need to set up
现在我需要在这里建立数据库
MongoDB now of course I have spring
MongoDB现在当然有 Spring
boots so spring boots can auto configure
靴子，这样 spring boot 可以自动配置
a connection factory to talk to the
连接工厂与
database and we can use the auto
数据库，我们可以使用自动
configuration to create a connection
配置以创建连接
factory and to create a MongoDB template
工厂并创建一个MongoDB模板
and all that stuff I could do all that
所有这些我可以做的
as you know by myself here but instead
如您本人所知，而是
I'm gonna use a test slice so test slice
我要使用一个测试切片，所以测试切片
is a a thing that lets us activate
是让我们激活的东西
certain parts of the application context
应用程序上下文的某些部分
in spring and then expose that or you
在 Spring ，然后揭露那个或你
know take advantage of that in testing
知道在测试中利用这一点
without having to instant ATAR and
无需立即使用ATAR和
construct the entire spring application
构建整个spring应用程序
context because I don't really want to
上下文，因为我真的不想
test the web tier here when all I'm
当我全部都在这里测试网络层
trying to do they don't think under test
试图做到他们不认为受测
the the variant in this case is the
在这种情况下的变体是
persistence logic and specifically the
持久逻辑，特别是
persistent project dealing with MongoDB
处理MongoDB的持久项目
so all the rest of that stuff can just
所以其余所有这些东西都可以
be sort of ignored for now it's
现在被忽略了
invariant and it's not under test so why
不变的，它不在测试中，为什么
bother instantiating those objects just
只需实例化这些对象
to be able to write this test and the
能够编写此测试以及
alternative of course is I don't write
另一种选择当然是我不写
any of it I don't let all rather I write
我不允许任何人写
all of it I don't let the spring do any
我不让 Spring 做任何事
of the work and which is a I think
的工作，这是我认为
that's a much worse alternative I'd much
那是我更糟糕的选择
rather not have to duplicate the recipe
而不需要重复配方
for constructing these objects between
用于在之间构造这些对象
my test and the actual production code
我的测试和实际生产代码
so I'm gonna go with these test slices
所以我要去这些测试片
and one of the one way you can do that
这是您可以做到这一点的一种方法
is we can take data among
我们可以在
and then I say that this is going to run
然后我说这将要运行
run with spring rena dot class so here
与 Spring 瑞纳点班一起运行所以这里
I'm telling spring boot that this is a
我告诉Spring Boot这是一个
spring this is one Sun Jane improperly J
Spring ，这是一个不当的太阳珍妮
unit four here this is a class that it's
第四单元这是一门课
gonna be managed by spring and it's
会在 Spring 之前进行管理
gonna be the lifecycle of this object
将成为该对象的生命周期
and the injected fields and all that
以及注入的字段和所有其他
will be managed by spring and I'm
将在 Spring 之前管理，我是
telling spring that this is a thing that
告诉 Spring 这件事
expects all the bits to do with MongoDB
希望所有位都与MongoDB有关
to be present and with that I can inject
在场，我可以注入
a reactive Mongo template
反应性Mongo模板
okay so reactive Mongo template and what
好吧，那么反应灵敏的Mongo模板以及什么
I want to do is I want to write some
我想写的是
data so I'm gonna write some data and
数据，所以我要写一些数据，
then I'm gonna prove that that data
那我要证明那个数据
exists so let's create a reactive
存在，让我们创建一个反应式
publisher and again this is a reactive
发布者，这又是一个反应
publisher we've looked at the reactive
发布商，我们已经研究了反应式
stream specification a number of times
流规范多次
before so let's see one reservation
在此之前，让我们来看一个预订
no.2 and I'm going to map each one of
2号，我要映射每个
these reservations into the database so
这些保留到数据库中，这样
this dot reactive reactive Mongo -
此点反应式反应式Mongo-
template that's save and when we save
保存的模板以及我们保存的时间
our what we get is a publisher of
我们得到的是
publisher publish on its own so I'm
出版商自行发布，所以我
going to flatmap and there's our
去平面图，有我们的
publisher a reactive publisher our
发布者反应性发布者我们
stream of data right our saved records
数据流直接保存的记录
so there's that saved and of course what
所以有节省，当然还有
I really want to do is I want to leet
我真的想做的就是想跳
everything first
一切先
so I say reactive Mongo template delete
所以我说反应性Mongo模板删除
all or you know drop collection or
全部或您知道液滴收集或
something like this that's fine with
像这样的东西很好用
that
那
all data saved so we can say let's see
所有数据已保存，所以我们可以说让我们看看
drop collection and we're going to drop
删除集合，我们将删除
the collection called reservation class
称为预订类的集合
and then we're gonna write this data
然后我们要写这些数据
saved and then what do we want to do
保存，然后我们要做什么
well we want to confirm that if we then
好吧，我们想确认一下，如果
pull the data back out for example like
拉回数据，例如
so reservation reactive on the template
所以预留对模板是被动的
that find all reservation dot class we
找到所有保留点类
expect that to have we expect that to
期望拥有我们期望
emit two records don'twe and we expect
发出两个记录，我们不希望
those
那些
to records to have a certain shape that
记录有一定的形状
should have one field called reservation
应该有一个称为保留的字段
name whose values are one and two
名称，其值为一和二
respectively and their ID fields should
分别，其ID字段应
ideally be non no so interaction here
理想情况下请不要互动
okay now this is a reactive pipeline so
好了，这是一个反应性管道，所以
really I'm kind of mixing the set up
真的，我有点混合设置
behavior of this test and teardown
此测试的行为和拆卸
behavior with the actual test itself and
实际测试本身的行为以及
the reason is because I can't rely on
原因是因为我不能依靠
things that execute in the tests such as
在测试中执行的事情，例如
been before method actually executing
在方法实际执行之前
before the logic in the test itself that
在测试本身的逻辑之前
is to say this is a reactive pipeline
就是说这是一个反应性管道
who knows what thread on which these
谁知道这些线程在哪个线程上
things will run and so I'm just gonna
事情会继续下去，所以我会
string them together I'm gonna say
把他们绑在一起，我要说
delete everything save the data and then
删除所有内容，然后保存数据，然后
prove that when I save it I can pull it
证明当我保存它可以拉它
back out again and get the result I'm
再次退出并得到我的结果
expecting I'm expecting that there's
期待我期待着
gonna be just two records okay and in
将会只有两个记录
order to prove that I'm gonna use the
为了证明我要使用
step verifier this is a nice API in
步骤验证程序，这是一个不错的API
spring web flex the reactive web runtime
Spring Web Flex反应式Web运行时
I'm gonna say create a verifier on that
我要说的是创建一个验证器
publisher and I want to expect that when
发布商，我希望当
I write the data you know that they
我写的数据你知道他们
match this predicate so I'm gonna create
匹配这个谓词，所以我要创建
a predicate here that matches a
这里的谓词与
reservation okay so a new predicate
保留好，所以有一个新的谓词
alright and here I'll say reservation
好了，我在这里说预订
get reservation name equals one or
获得预订名称等于一或
reservation dot get reservation name
预订点获取预订名称
equals two okay so there's my very
等于两个好，所以我的
simple predicate object I'm just going
我要去的简单谓词对象
to confirm that the data that we
确认我们的数据
expected to have been written has indeed
期望已经写的确实
been written and we also want to confirm
被写，我们也想确认
that reservation dot ID is not know so
那个保留点ID不知道
reservation get ID
预订获取ID
and there we are
我们在那里
so it's a little bit of a complicated
所以有点复杂
twisted little test but I'm saying this
扭曲了一点考验，但我是在说这个
has to be not an old and it has to be
必须不是一个旧的，它必须是
one or two okay very very simple and
一两个好吧，非常非常简单，
that predicate I'll pass into here and
这个谓词我会进入这里
then I'll say I want to verify a
那么我会说我想验证
complete okay so let's let's see what we
完成吧，让我们看看我们
get when we run this code now let's see
现在，当我们运行此代码时，让我们看看
here we go whoops recompiling run
在这里，我们去whoops重新编译运行
okay
好的
ah right there's two records that were
嗯，有两个记录是
admitted so I need to I need to account
承认，所以我需要我要考虑
for both of those by expecting them both
通过期望他们两个
so I'm gonna say expect next
所以我要说下一个期待
it matches twice and though that's why I
它匹配两次，但这就是为什么我
even caught I even accounted for both of
甚至抓到我什至都占了
them being admitted but didn't actually
他们被录取，但实际上并没有
run the tester correctly alright so
正确运行测试仪，这样
there we go so now we know that if we
我们去了那里，所以现在我们知道，如果我们
use the stock standard sort of reactive
使用库存标准的反应型
Mongo template that we can write data to
我们可以向其中写入数据的Mongo模板
the database as we expect okay that's
我们期望的数据库是
you know interesting in itself and give
你知道本身很有趣，并给予
us a chance to see the step here fire
我们有机会看到这里的台阶
the step verifier is really the
步骤验证器确实是
workhorse of the reactive sort of
反应性的主力
testing suite all the things we're gonna
测试套件，我们要做的所有事情
do in a reactive world a lot of the time
很多时候在反应性世界中做
you're gonna find yourself we will come
你会发现自己，我们会来
in and step verify and one thing that's
在一步验证，这是一件事
really nice is that there's even a
真的很好，甚至有一个
virtual time so I can say here's a
虚拟时间，所以我可以说这是一个
publisher I can give it a publisher that
发布者我可以给它一个发布者
it's asking for and it'll you know I can
它要的，你会知道我可以的
then tell it to to to wait right I can
然后告诉它要等我就可以
tell it to wait a duration for example
告诉它等待一段时间，例如
and I can I can say okay this publisher
我可以说这发行人好
is gonna admit you know a new value
会承认你知道一个新的价值
every second whatever publish I give it
每秒钟我发布的内容
in this case and the it's just a flux
在这种情况下，它只是一个流量
does just a that's not gonna delay
只是不会延迟
elements duration of seconds one so here
元素秒的持续时间，所以这里
I'm actually giving it a I'm dynamically
我实际上是给它一个动态的
loading a publisher that would produce
加载将产生
new values every second I'm saying then
我说的是每秒新价值
wait you know ten seconds and then
等你知道十秒钟，然后
verify complete and I can do I can
验证完成，我可以
verify you know expect you know expect
验证您知道期望您知道期望
next couch and that'll be two right I'm
下一张沙发，那是我的两个
expecting two records so here I'm
期待两个记录，所以我在这里
actually creating a publisher that has a
实际上创建的发布商具有
scheduler it takes me taking advantage
调度程序需要我利用
of the scheduler and yet I'm not I'm not
调度程序，但我不是，我不是
gonna wait you know ten seconds actually
要等你知道十秒钟
it's virtual fake I'm actually mocking
这是我实际上在嘲笑的虚拟假货
out the scheduler that's in play here
在这里发挥作用的调度程序
and this is one of those things that you
这是你其中的一件事
should be aware
应该知道
remember when you write reactive code
记住当您编写反应式代码时
time is a dimension of the API right you
时间是API的维度，对吧
can actually work with it you can plan
可以实际使用它，您可以计划
around it you can you can you can assume
围绕它，你可以，你可以假设
it's there right so so this is one of
就在那里，所以这是其中之一
the nice things about the verifier you
关于验证者的美好之处
can do all sorts
可以做各种各样的事
of things with stiff verifier here I've
我在这里用僵硬的验证程序
just verified you know if I say create
刚刚验证您知道我是否说创建
and then stay whatever and then I can
然后留下任何东西，然后我可以
say I want to expect the next count
说我想期待下一次
don't expect certain results I can
不要期望我能得到某些结果
expect that some things subscribe to a
期望某些东西订阅
certain thing I can expect all sorts of
我可以期待各种各样的东西
interesting things here I can expect
我可以期待这里有趣的事情
that there's an error for example
例如有一个错误
they've got passed into the on arrow
他们已经通过了on箭头
method of the subscriber all sorts of
订户的各种方法
interesting things okay so we are gonna
有趣的事情好了，所以我们要
take advantage it as we have okay so now
利用它，因为我们现在可以了
we have we have a basic entity what else
我们有一个基本的实体
do we want it well I suppose we I
我们想要它吗我想我们
suppose now that we've got that I want
假设现在我们有了我想要的
to create a repository don't I so I
创建存储库不是吗，所以我
wanna create a repository I would say
我想说一个仓库
reservation repository test and that
预留存储库测试以及
repository test is going to be used to
存储库测试将用于
verify that you know when we issue a
验证您知道我们何时发出
query that we get the right results back
查询我们获得正确的结果
so you don't find all by reservation
因此您无法通过预订找到全部
name throws exception okay and I'm gonna
名字抛出异常好了，我要
create spring winner over sorry run with
创建 Spring 赢家，以对不起与
split up okay and again data among with
拆分好，然后再次与
test goody so there's that now what I
测试好东西，所以现在我
want to do is I'm gonna create a simple
我要做的就是创建一个简单的
example I'm saying Auto wired private
例子我是说自动有线私人
reservation repository and of course
预订库，当然
here we are lacking production code so
这里我们缺少生产代码，所以
with the IDE to the walking and it's
用IDE来走路，它是
going to be an interface it extends the
将成为一个接口，它扩展了
reactive Mongo repository managing
反应性Mongo资料库管理
entities of type reservation whose
其预订类型的实体
primary keys of type string I don't need
我不需要的字符串类型的主键
to test these methods I know full well
测试这些方法我很了解
that the reactive methods directive you
反应性方法指令你
know crud style methods that are implied
知道暗含的样式方法
on this are gonna work right that's not
在这将是正确的，不是
the goal here the goal is to test my
这里的目标是测试我的
custom finder methods
自定义查找器方法
for example this one find by reservation
例如，这个是通过预订找到的
name string RN that will get turned into
将变成的名称字符串RN
Abby's on query that we can then you
艾比（Abby）有疑问，我们可以为您
know interrogate we can say okay find
知道询问我们可以说好找到
all the records in the and that in that
和中的所有记录
collection or a reservation name : RN
预订或预订名称：RN
right okay so there's that there's our
好吧，所以有我们的
custom query let's test that and the way
自定义查询让我们测试一下方式
we can test that is by first of all
我们可以首先测试一下
clearing out the database and then
清除数据库，然后
writing some data to it and then and
向其中写入一些数据，然后
then pulling it back out again by that
然后再把它拉出来
query so same as before
查询与以前一样
okay okay but this time we'll say if
好吧好吧，但是这次我们要说
Flex dive just a B dot map I guess we
Flex潜水只是一个B点图，我想我们
can just do flat map okay name new
可以做平面地图好吧名字新
reservation okay no name and we want to
保留好吧，没有名字，我们想
save that don't me so we're gonna say
拯救那不是我，所以我们要说
this dot reservation allows for that
这个点保留允许
save alrighty so there's the the whole
保存好，所以整个
thing and I'm gonna save the data all
的东西，我要保存所有的数据
right and I'm gonna you know now that we
对，我要知道，我们
know that it's been saved we want to
知道它已经保存了，我们想
actually clean up to anyway so we want
无论如何实际上要清理，所以我们想要
to say this dot reservation imposter
说点保留冒名顶替者
delete all then passing in that then
删除所有然后传递的那个
this dot reservation illustrious find
这个点保留杰出
all by reservation name and you know
全部以预订名称命名，您知道
let's try this again let's do C's D and
让我们再试一次让我们做C的D
C again so we'll have several records in
再次C，所以我们将在
there and I'm gonna look for C and I'm
在那里，我要寻找C，我是
gonna then verify that the result of all
然后验证所有结果
this is as we expect we expect to have
正如我们期望的那样
to record to type C so let's say step
记录以键入C，所以我们说步骤
verifier dot create flux verify or
验证点创建通量验证或
expect rather next matches or expect
期待下一场比赛或期待
next count it's gonna be to verify
下一次计数将是要验证
complete alright so there's our
完全正确，所以我们有
repository so I'm just I'm writing data
存储库，所以我只是在写数据
to the database I'm deleting everything
到数据库，我正在删除所有内容
first of all sorry I'm deleting
首先，抱歉，我要删除
everything first then I'm going to be
一切先，然后我要成为
running data to the database and then
运行数据到数据库，然后
I'll plug it you know I'll pull it back
我会插上它，你知道我会把它拉回来的
out again using this finder which should
再次使用这个取景器
only match the results that have C as
仅匹配具有C作为的结果
the name so let's try that
这个名字，所以让我们尝试
all right that seems that worked awesome
好吧，看起来很棒
so now what do we need to do well we've
所以现在我们需要做的很好
got that working um I think we should
嗯，我认为我们应该
test our REST API we've got spring data
测试我们的REST API，我们有spring数据
we've got the entity we've got the
我们有实体，我们有
finder method that's all working just
搜寻器方法就可以了
fine so so now um let's let's test the
很好，所以现在让我们测试一下
rest API so let's build a simple REST
rest API，让我们构建一个简单的REST
API we're gonna say reservation rest
API，我们要说休息
test okay and here I'm going to use a
测试还可以，这里我将使用
different slice here that you know thus
你在这里知道的不同切片
far we've used web envy web we've used
到目前为止，我们已经使用过网络羡慕网络
data Mongo test now I'm gonna use web
数据Mongo测试，现在我要使用网络
flex test right it's a web flex test and
flex test right这是一个Web flex测试，
run with spring runner dot class all
与 Spring 跑垒员全班一起跑步
right and here we're going to test that
对，在这里我们要测试
when we make a call to the HTTP GET we
当我们调用HTTP GET时，
make an HTTP GET call to a reservations
拨打HTTP GET预订电话
endpoint that we should get the data
我们应该获取数据的端点
back that we expect so let's try that
返回我们期望的，让我们尝试一下
out so public void get all reservations
出去所以公共无效得到所有保留
throws exception and in order to make
抛出异常并为了使
this call we're not going to use the
这个电话我们不会使用
mahkum you see client instead we use the
mahkum，您看到客户，而是使用
web test client which is the reactive
网络测试客户端
equivalent in this new world all right
等同于这个新世界
it's a web test client not web flex test
这是一个Web测试客户端，而不是Web Flex测试
web test client all righty so and I'm
网络测试客户端没问题，所以我
gonna say dot get dot URI HTTP localhost
要说点获取点URI HTTP本地主机
8080 for slash reservations dot exchange
8080用于斜线保留点交换
and here oh well here we have to poke at
在这里，哦，在这里，我们必须戳一下
the resulting data don't mean I want to
结果数据并不意味着我要
poke at the the results that come back
戳一下返回的结果
from this REST API so I guess I want to
从这个REST API，所以我想我想
assert certain things I want to search
断言某些我想搜索的东西
for example the status is okay I want to
例如，状态还可以，我想
expect that there's a content type
期望有一种内容类型
header that has a certain value right
具有一定值的标头
and then finally I want to poke at the
最后我想戳一下
data I want to
我想要的数据
to expect that the body matches a
期望身体与
certain structure so I'm gonna say that
某种结构，所以我要说
it has a adjacent path match so I think
它具有相邻的路径匹配，所以我认为
I'm gonna say match the first prem first
我要说先比赛第一场比赛
the element in the array and that should
数组中的元素，应该
be equal to let's say 1 i want to match
等于1我要匹配
the first reservation name right and
第一预订名称的权利和
that should be equal to a alright and
应该等于好的
you know we could go further let's do
你知道我们可以走得更远
that let's go further let's just say
让我们走的更远，让我们说
let's copy this and this way we can
让我们复制这个，这样我们可以
confirm that we have a multivalued array
确认我们有一个多值数组
and this one would be called B all right
这将被称为B
there we go so there's our web test
我们去了，所以有我们的网络测试
client and you know that's gonna fail
客户，你知道那会失败
obviously we haven't written the rest in
显然，我们没有把其余的写在
point but let's just go ahead and try it
点，但让我们继续尝试一下
see what we get
看看我们得到了什么
okay so first of all that's not gonna
好吧，首先，那不是
work obviously that's not gonna work
工作显然是行不通的
because for for so let's fix that right
因为为此，让我们来解决这个问题
now let's go back to our production code
现在让我们回到生产代码
and our production code we can create a
和我们的生产代码，我们可以创建一个
new class down here class reservation
新班下课预定
rest configuration okay and here I'm
休息配置好了，我在这里
going to create a functional reactive
将创建一个功能性反应
endpoint using the Spring Framework five
端点使用Spring Framework五
function reactive API so server response
功能性反应式API，因此服务器响应
routes at configuration and in order to
路由配置并为了
create that endpoint I'm going to inject
创建我将要注入的端点
my black hang I can actually just do
我的黑坑我实际上可以做
that here can't die so we'll say inject
这里不会死的，所以我们说注射
the reservation repository alright I
保留资料库好吧我
turn router function this dot route
将此点转为路由器功能
request predicate s-- dot get four slash
请求谓词s-点得到四个斜杠
reservations and new handler function
保留和新的处理程序功能
and the goal here you know as before
和这里的目标一样
I've done this particular endpoint a
我已经完成了这个特定的端点
million five times so I know that this
五次，所以我知道
is going to work but it's helpful to
将要工作，但对
define this the contract ahead of time
提前定义合同
to think about explicitly what I want
明确思考我想要什么
this endpoint to do and by running the
通过运行该端点来执行
test I kind of know that this is I'm
测试我有点知道这是我
gonna expect this to provide a content
会期望这将提供内容
type of application type of Jason utf-8
应用程序类型Jason utf-8
I want the body to be derived from the
我希望身体是从
repository so we'll say it's a final and
仓库，所以我们说这是最终的
the kind of data that we're sending back
我们发回的数据类型
here is reactive publisher of
这是
reservations now this is a bit verbose
现在保留，这有点冗长
so let's clean it up here using a nice
所以我们在这里用一个不错的东西清理一下
Java 8 functional reactive lambda
Java 8功能反应式Lambda
centric you know static import friendly
中心，你知道静态导入友好
API okay all right look at that okay so
API好吧，好吧，看好吧
we've got now our data and that's it
现在我们有了数据，仅此而已
that's our functional reactive endpoint
那就是我们的功能性反应终点
right there's a very simple endpoint
对，有一个非常简单的终点
let's now confirm that this works it
现在让我们确认这是否可行
still won't
仍然不会
as we'll see in a second but for a
我们将在第二秒看到
different reason all right so it is
不同的原因没事吧
saying that it can't find this resting
说它找不到这个休息
point that's because our test code
这是因为我们的测试代码
doesn't know about the rest
不知道其余的
configuration we need to actually
我们实际需要的配置
actually explicitly bring it in which we
实际上明确地把它带入我们
can do like so and it's still gonna fail
可以这样做，但仍然会失败
still gonna fail that's pretty
仍然会失败，这很漂亮
depressing isn't it but watch all right
压抑是不是但是要注意
and the reason it failed is because
它失败的原因是
there is no such being of type
没有这样的存在
reservation repository so again this is
保留资源库，所以这又是
a test slice this test slice tells
该测试切片告诉的测试切片
spring to selectively load the objects
Spring 以选择性地加载对象
related to the thing under which would
与将要发生的事情有关
you know under test in this case the web
您知道在这种情况下正在测试中的网络
tier which means that all the other
层，这意味着所有其他
things like the mom would it be
像妈妈这样的事情
repository for example is not you know
例如不是您知道存储库
they're not being loaded they're not
他们没有被加载，他们没有
being instantiated nothing is being done
被实例化什么也没做
in that in a particular thing so we need
在那件事上，所以我们需要
to to mock out that repository and we
来模拟那个仓库，我们
know that in order for us to make this
知道为了让我们做到这一点
rest call I inject this reservation
休息电话我要为此保留
repository so clearly we need that
仓库如此明确，我们需要
reservation repository and yet I'm not
预订资料库，但我不是
I'm not you know it doesn't exist it's
我不是你知道它不存在
not being instant it's not making
不是瞬间，不是
figures so I need to mock out that
数字，所以我需要模拟一下
object and the easiest way to do that is
对象，最简单的方法是
to use the Spring Framework 1.4 mock
使用Spring Framework 1.4模拟
bean sanitation and what this does is it
bean 卫生，这是做什么的
lets me um you know tell spring to
让我，你知道告诉 Spring
replace this bean to replace any
替换这个bean来替换任何
instance of this bean of this type with
此类型的bean的实例
this mockito mock that is gonna be
这个mockito模拟将
created for us if it doesn't already
为我们创建（如果尚未创建）
exist in the application context if the
如果应用程序上下文中存在
bean if there is no bean of type
bean，如果没有类型的bean
reservation repository as in this case
在这种情况下，保留库
then one will be created and it'll be a
然后将创建一个
mock what we want is a stub though not a
模拟我们想要的是一个存根，虽然不是
mock so we're gonna say mockito dot when
模拟，所以我们要说模拟点
this that reservation or pause right and
这个保留或暂停权利，
find all and when you say then return
找到所有，当你说然后返回
flux dot just new reservation say one a
通量点只是新的保留说一个
new reservation to be all right so now
新的保留可以，所以现在
we have told it we really pre-programmed
我们已经告诉我们我们真的已经预先设定好了
our mock
我们的模拟
and now it's a stub right it has a it's
现在是一个存根，它有一个
gonna respond with with data that weeks
会用那几周的数据回应
we've given it to respond with okay so
我们已经给它回应了，所以
start that up
开始
okay not bad so we've got now a REST API
好的，还不错，所以我们现在有了REST API
we've got we've been we're able to test
我们已经得到了我们能够测试
all the way from the right REST API all
从正确的REST API一直
the way down to the lowest tiers each
下降到最低层的方式
test is really fast
测试真的很快
this took 333 milliseconds to start up
这花费了333毫秒的启动时间
the web's web test hit the endpoint
网络的网络测试达到了终点
confirm that the bytes that come back to
确认返回的字节
look like the bytes would expect if we
看起来如果我们期望字节
were to make an HTTP endpoint request
发出HTTP端点请求
you know in an actual sort of live fire
你知道在一种实际的生火中
example okay and we also didn't pay the
例子还可以，我们也没有支付
cost of you know configuring all the
您知道配置所有
database stuff right now I want to build
现在我要构建数据库的东西
a client so we've got a service let's
客户，所以我们有服务，让我们
build a client here I'm gonna go back
在这里建立客户我要回去
and I'll build a client called the
我将建立一个名为
consumer and again we'll use 2.11 one
消费者，我们将再次使用2.11
when use the stub runner support and
使用存根运行器支持时
we're gonna use Lombok I'm gonna use a
我们要用龙目岛我要用
reactive web support we don't need of
我们不需要的反应式网络支持
course MongoDB here so I'll hit generate
当然这里有MongoDB，所以我将点击generate
that gives a consumer and we'll go back
给消费者，我们会回去
to our build you a little consumer and
为我们建立了一个小消费者，
now what we want to do is want to drive
现在我们要做的就是开车
it we're gonna build a client that we
我们将建立一个客户，我们
can use to talk to our our REST API okay
可以用来和我们的REST API对话
so I go to the consumer application go
所以我去消费者应用程序去
to the test code for the consumer
消费者的测试代码
application proper all right now same as
现在正确的应用程序与
before we're gonna go ahead and just you
在我们继续前进之前，只有你
know sort of actually I guess we can
我知道我们实际上可以
just keep this this is fine but you know
保持这个很好，但是你知道
we don't we've only got a one test here
我们不是，我们只有一个测试
so let's rename it to be a little bit
所以我们重命名一下
more appropriate reservation client best
更合适的预订客户最好
all right and we want to test that we
好的，我们要测试一下
can get all reservations goody
可以得到所有的预订好东西
and when test that I'm gonna throw
当我测试要扔的时候
exception if we need to and in order to
例外，如果我们需要并且为了
make this call we're going to inject the
拨打电话，我们将注入
reservation client which of course since
预订客户当然
we haven't defined it yet isn't gonna go
我们还没有定义它不会继续
very far right we're not gonna get very
非常远的权利，我们不会得到非常
far without that client let's go ahead
没有那个客户，我们继续前进
and create it and the client will have a
并创建它，客户端将有一个
very simple job given a request we turn
给我们一个请求，一个非常简单的工作
a publisher of reservations and of
保留和发行人
course we don't have the publisher
当然我们没有出版商
whereas a reservation
而保留
rather so we need to define that I can
而是我们需要定义我可以
do that here okay
在这里做
quite the client-side detail private
相当详细的客户端细节
string name private string ID all right
字符串名称私有字符串ID可以
now there's a client-side representation
现在有一个客户端表示
we want the Lombok bits to make the rest
我们想要龙目岛的其余部分
eat here okay
在这里吃饭好吗
and now with that in place I need to go
现在有了适当的位置，我需要走
back to my client code and I'm gonna say
回到我的客户代码，我要说
this dot client dot get all reservations
这个点客户端点得到所有保留
okay and we want to say step verifier
好吧，我们要说一步验证器
dot create all reservations and we'll
点创建所有保留，我们将
expect what do we expect well I expect
期待我们期待什么
that we're gonna have let's say two
我们要说两个
records okay so two records and so we'll
记录好，所以有两个记录，所以我们将
give it a predicate and the predicate
给它一个谓词和谓词
will be pretty straightforward equals
将非常简单等于
new predicate and we'll say P and we'll
新的谓词，我们将说P，我们将
verify complete another predicate I'm
验证我是否完成另一个谓词
gonna say I'm you know same as before us
会说我和你一样
both we want to say get ID string utils
我们都想说得到ID字符串utils
dot as text okay and reservation dot get
点作为文本可以，保留点得到
name equals let's say Jane or
名字等于简或
reservation dot get name equals John
保留点获取名称等于John
okay so there's our super simple
好，所以我们的超级简单
predicate we just place that like so
谓词我们只是像这样放置
alright good now
好吧，现在
that's our very simple predicate that's
这是我们非常简单的谓词
a simple logic let's go ahead and run
一个简单的逻辑，让我们继续运行
this I have every confidence that it's
我完全有信心
well it's probably not gonna work let's
好吧，那可能行不通，让我们
just go ahead and try it though you
只是继续尝试，尽管你
never know
永远不知道
good work could be magic in the air
好的工作可能会变得神奇
might be that kind of night
可能是那样的夜晚
well it gave us hope there didn't it for
好吧，这给了我们希望，没有
a split second now I wanted to believe
现在我想相信
you know but not even close so we're we
你知道但还没有结束，所以我们
don't even have a reservation client let
甚至没有预订客户让
alone a working one we don't as far as
一个工作的人，我们远没有
spring is concerned this doesn't even
Spring 担心，这甚至没有
exist yet so so that won't get us far
存在，所以不会使我们走得更远
and oh yeah sure we could start again
哦，是的，我们可以再次开始
let's try that again I guess but I think
让我再试一次，但我想
we can fit we can surmise that this
我们可以适应，我们可以推测
isn't gonna get very far because we're
不会走的太远，因为我们
we don't have anything happening here so
我们这里什么也没发生
let's take that a step further we need a
让我们更进一步，我们需要一个
web client the reactive web client is a
Web客户端反应式Web客户端是一个
HTTP client that we can use to make rest
我们可以用来休息的HTTP客户端
calls reactively in order for that to
反应性地调用以便
work we would need a beam of type web
工作，我们将需要一个类型的网梁
client so here we are web client and we
客户，所以这里我们是网络客户，我们
need the web client builder and builder
需要Web客户端构建器和构建器
dot build so with that in place we can
点构建，这样我们就可以
say this dot web client dot get dot URI
说这个点网络客户端点得到点URI
HTTP localhost 8080 for slash
HTTP本地主机8080的斜线
reservations dot retrieve dot body tooth
保留点取回点身体牙齿
flux is gonna be a reservation class and
助焊剂将成为保留课程，
that's it that's our whole thing
这就是我们的全部
now that should surely work of course
现在当然应该可以工作
right go ahead and try that out
正确，继续尝试
not so much and I think we could all
没那么多，我想我们都可以
kind of see that coming even with a
看到即使有一个
perfectly working client we're just not
完美的客户，我们只是没有
gonna get very far if we don't have a
如果我们没有一个，它将走得很远
working service and while we do have a
工作服务，而我们确实有一个
working service it's not running and I
工作服务没有运行，我
really don't want to have to run it in
真的不想在其中运行
order to be able to confirm that this
为了能够确认这一点
works that would be you know pretty
你会很漂亮的作品
hostile it's there's a you know there's
敌对的是那里，你知道那里的
a number of things we could do here we
我们可以在这里做很多事情
could start up the whole system and and
可以启动整个系统，并且
test it but that's hardly a unit test or
测试它，但这几乎不是单元测试或
even a lightweight sort of component
甚至是轻量级的组件
test that would be more like an
测试更像是
integration test or an end-to-end test
集成测试或端到端测试
or a smoke test and that's just that's a
或烟雾测试，那就是
non-starter with any kind of sufficient
没有足够的启动器
scale you know in in the English
你用英语知道的比例
language a friendly thing you could say
语言你可以说的友好的话
to somebody is hello or welcome if
向某人问好或欢迎
somebody comes to work with you if they
如果有人来和你一起工作
come on if they join your team if they
如果他们加入您的团队，那就来吧
want to unwrap a very friendly thing to
想拆开一件非常友好的东西
say in English is to say welcome and how
用英语说是欢迎和如何
may I help you a very hostile thing in
我可以帮你一个非常敌对的事情吗
the English language is to say here
这里要说英语
deploy this kubernetes cluster right
正确部署这个kubernetes集群
nothing makes enemies of somebody faster
没有什么可以使某人的敌人更快
then sticking them with 100 virtual
然后贴上100个虚拟
machines I'm saying figure that out and
我说的是机器
then you can start to you can start
那么你可以开始，你可以开始
developing this little micro service
开发这个小微服务
that that you're trying to work on so we
您正在尝试的工作，所以我们
need to get around that one thing we
需要绕过那件事，我们
could do is mock out this REST API I
可以做的就是模拟这个REST API
know
知道
odd but we can do it so let's think
奇怪，但我们可以做到，所以让我们考虑一下
about that how would we do that we can
关于我们该怎么做，我们可以
use wire mock wire mock is an API so we
使用电线模拟电线模拟是一个API，因此我们
can say Auto configure wire mock and we
可以说自动配置电线模拟，我们
want this to run on port 8080 and our
希望它在端口8080上运行
wire mock API is going to provide a rest
电线模拟API将提供休息
tape it's gonna stand up a fake REST API
磁带会站起来假的REST API
that that responds you know with
那回应你知道的
pre-programmed responses so in require
预编程的响应，因此需要
mock stub for wire mock dot ini'
电线的模拟存根模拟点ini'
Cuauhtemoc URL matching for slash
Cuauhtemoc URL匹配斜杠
reservations and whatever I do wanna say
保留和我想说的一切
that it'll return wire mock a response
它将返回电线模拟响应
with a header HTTP headers dot content
带标头HTTP标头的点内容
type
类型
HTTP headers dot content type media type
HTTP标头点内容类型媒体类型
application JSON utf-8 value okay
应用程序JSON utf-8值还可以
and with header that's right we wanna I
和正确的标题，我们想
guess that we're done with that we're
猜想我们已经完成了
now melissa with status a should be
现在状态为a的梅利莎应该是
status dot okay doesn't value and then
状态点好没值，然后
finally with a body I'm going to just
终于有了一个身体，我要去
provide a a pre-programmed string body
提供一个预编程的字符串体
here with some data in it and that's it
这里有一些数据就是这样
that's the structure of the thing that
那就是事物的结构
when returned so let's go ahead and hand
返回时，让我们继续前进
craft the response here I cannot wait
在这里制作我无法等待的回应
for Java twelve multi-line strings oh
Java的十二个多行字符串哦
haha but I'm in the meantime we'll just
哈哈，但与此同时我只是
do this the old-fashioned way and string
用老式的方式和字符串来执行此操作
literals raw strings and jobs well
文字原始字符串和工作很好
that's gonna be great
那会很棒
this is also dead simple to do in Scala
这在Scala中也很简单
goofy or Kotlin right now we don't have
高飞或Kotlin现在我们没有
to wait but you know Yolo so ID one
等待，但是你知道Yolo，所以我一个
let's get rid of that keep things a
让我们摆脱它，让事情变得
little pair winning and we want to say
小双赢，我们想说
name and this will be Jane okay there's
名字，这将是简，好的
our first record and John alright and
我们的第一张唱片，约翰好吧，
that'll be too cool so there we go
那太酷了，所以我们去了
there's our hard-coded jason string that
有我们的硬编码杰森字符串，
were expecting to be put back to anybody
期望被放回任何人
who in the course of this test goes to
在测试过程中谁去
localhost 8080 or whatever port this
本地主机8080或任何此端口
thing is running on in this case port
在这种情况下，端口正在运行
8080 could be specified as much up here
在这里可以指定8080
and then asks you know using HTTP GET
然后询问您是否知道使用HTTP GET
request for this content and that will
请求此内容，这将
of course be dismantled the whole thing
当然要拆掉整个东西
this whole fake server will spin up and
这整个假服务器将旋转起来，
then be dismantled by the time this
然后在这个时候被拆除
thing it shuts down by the time the test
测试时它关闭的东西
shuts down so let's try that what do you
关闭，让我们尝试一下
think
认为
okay when do we miss ah I have to do
好吧，我们什么时候想念啊，我要做
this twice don't same as before
这两次与以前不同
already that seems to be happy that's
已经很高兴了
awesome that's working that's what we
很棒，这就是我们正在做的
expected everything would seem to be
预期一切似乎
okay we've got a green client we've got
好吧，我们有一个绿色的客户，我们有
a green consumer and a green service and
绿色消费者和绿色服务，以及
green producer and yet you know
绿色生产者，但你知道
punchline I think is pretty clear which
我认为很清楚
is that green though they are these
那是绿色吗
things don't actually work and the
事情实际上不起作用，并且
reason is because we're building this
原因是因为我们正在建立这个
whole client under a faulty assumption
错误假设下的整个客户
somewhere along the line I I fed
沿第二条路线喂食
fingered the name of the attribute and
指望属性的名称，
it went from reservation name to name
它从保留名称到名称
and so while it's green in the client
因此，尽管客户端绿色
it's actually a completely different
实际上是完全不同的
type on the service right and so here
在服务上输入正确的信息，因此在这里
I've got reservation name that's what I
我有保留名就是我的名字
should've been using on the on the
应该一直在使用
producer side and the most sort of
生产者方面和最
deceptive part of this whole thing is
这整个事情的欺骗性部分是
that they're both green both both seem
他们俩都是绿色的，似乎都
to be both seem to think that everything
似乎都认为一切
is just fine and yet we would get to
很好，但是我们会
production presumably or at least
生产大概或至少
integration testing and find out that
集成测试并发现
this doesn't work at all green though
虽然这根本不起作用绿色
both sides are and that's a little
双方都是，这有点
that's a little you know that can shake
你知道那会动摇一点
you if you're expecting that to have
如果您希望有
already been caught and you know were we
已经被抓了，你知道我们吗
doing a monolith then this would be a
做一个整体，那么这将是一个
compiler error the compiler would tell
编译器会告诉编译器错误
you that you broke a thing upon which
你，你打破了一个东西
you're relying a type that is expected
您所依赖的是预期的类型
to work when something else binds to it
当其他东西绑定到它上去工作
you know a client consumed it and here
你知道一个客户消费了，在这里
we have a rest api our network contract
我们有一个REST API我们的网络合同
and that's just it's very stringent it
这就是非常严格的
so one way to get around this is to you
所以解决这个问题的一种方法是给你
know use RPC i suppose but then you lose
我想知道我会使用RPC，但是那你就输了
some of the benefits of the open web and
开放网络的一些好处和
if that's your that's your bag then of
如果那是你的那是你的包，那么
course that's not really an option is it
当然那不是一个选择
so what we want is to get confidence
所以我们想要获得信心
that the thing we're building is
我们正在建造的东西是
actually the thing that and the thing
实际上那个东西和那个东西
we're testing against is actually the
我们正在测试的实际上是
thing that exists in production so here
生产中存在的东西，所以在这里
what we do is we use consumer driven
我们要做的是使用消费者驱动的
contracts using spring cloud contract
使用Spring Cloud Contract的合约
now consumer driven contracts are fairly
现在，以消费者为导向的合同相当合理
straightforward they are a way to define
简单明了，它们是定义的方式
a test a unit test these contracts get
测试这些合同得到的单元测试
transpiled into into unit tests that
转换成单元测试
then get run against your code and it is
然后针对您的代码运行，它是
almost exactly as though we had written
几乎就像我们写的一样
this this uh
这个这个
the rest test that we wrote earlier and
我们之前写的其余测试
so that's what we're gonna do okay we're
这就是我们要做的，好吧，我们
gonna write a very simple test for our
要为我们编写一个非常简单的测试
application and that test is going to
应用程序，该测试将
it's going to extend some sort of base
它会扩展某种基础
test it has to do the same sort of setup
测试它是否必须执行相同的设置
in so on so let's go back to our
等等，让我们回到我们的
producer side here this is the service
生产者方面，这是服务
side I'm gonna use spring cloud contract
我要使用Spring Cloud Contract
and we're gonna configure that plug-in
我们将配置该插件
now I've got that plug-in configuration
现在我有了插件配置
laying around not one to be caught on
躺在周围没有人被抓住
unawares too often so there's that copy
太不知道了，所以有那个副本
and paste alright so I've got the
并粘贴好，所以我有
plug-in here daddy and so what that's
插件，爸爸，那是什么
doing is it's saying I've got the spring
就是说我有 Spring 了
cloud contract maven plugin on the
上的云合约Maven插件
producer side version 202 release and my
生产者方版本202和我的
contracts which we're gonna see in a
我们将在合同中看到的合同
moment these are actually groovy
这些实际上是时髦的
language artifacts that define a an
定义一个
interaction with a service they define
与他们定义的服务进行交互
how a client should talk to a given
客户应该如何与给定的人交谈
service they define what that client
服务他们定义那个客户
should expect from a given service and
应该从给定的服务中期望
that those expectations get turned into
这些期望变成了
tests which get exercised here on the
在这里进行的测试
service against our actual real API the
针对我们实际的真实API的服务
REST API and so if that is green then we
REST API，所以如果是绿色，那么我们
can install or deploy stub definitions
可以安装或部署存根定义
that you know basically a the
你基本上知道一个
configuration that is required to create
创建所需的配置
that wire mock API gets deployed and
电线模拟API被部署，
then now we can in the consumer side
那么现在我们可以在消费者方面
consume those stub definitions to stand
消耗那些存根定义
up a mock API that matches the reality
建立符合实际情况的模拟API
of this production service and so with
这项生产服务等等
that in mind let's create a very simple
考虑到这一点，让我们创建一个非常简单的
contract and the contract will get
合同，合同将得到
transpired by this plugin as I say this
我说的这个插件
is the enforcement part to the the
是执法的一部分
contract mechanism okay so here I'm
合同机制好，所以我在这里
gonna say source test
要说源测试
resources contracts alright
资源合同还可以
get a new file here should we turn all
在这里得到一个新文件，如果我们全部
reservations doc movie and here's just a
预订doc电影，这只是一个
gue VDSL that we can use request
gue我们可以使用的VDSL请求
responds and we describe the API so I'm
响应，我们描述了API，所以我
going to say when return should return
要说什么时候应该返回
all reservations okay and the request is
所有保留都可以，要求是
going to be to the URL called
将会转到称为
reservations the method it is gonna be
保留将要使用的方法
HT t get the response will be status
HT t得到的响应将是状态
code you know 200 I guess we can just
你知道的代码200我想我们可以
use H to be status here dot value and
使用H作为状态，此处是点值，
the content type or I guess the headers
内容类型或我猜标题
and C headers content type media type
和C标头内容类型媒体类型
dot application Jason utf-8 value and
点应用程序Jason utf-8值和
the body will be as follows I guess and
我猜身体会如下
we could use the GUI you know object
我们可以使用您知道的GUI对象
literal syntax here to create a Jason
文字语法在这里创建一个Jason
like structure and that's sort of an
像结构，有点像
option we could do that we can say
选项，我们可以做到，我们可以说
reservation name Jane ie to reservation
预订名称Jane即预订
name John alright now this is the Jason
叫约翰，好吧，这是杰森
like structure I could as easily use a
像结构，我可以轻松地使用
string right I could just do what I did
正确的字符串我可以做我所做的事
before and the Java code but of course
当然还有Java代码，但是
here it's groovy so it's much easier
这很古怪，所以更容易
just to say you know to write things
只是说你知道写东西
that look like JSON right there so you
就像JSON一样，所以您
know like that our ID one reservation
知道我们的ID一号预订
name Jane
名字简
okay so - John alright so there's our
好吧-约翰好吧，这是我们的
JSON output and we have multi-line
JSON输出，我们有多行
strings array and so that just works
字符串数组，这样就可以了
that's just actually the the content of
这实际上只是
the are the results so now we're
是结果，所以现在我们
expecting this to result in something
期望这会导致某些结果
that you know we're expecting that this
你知道我们期待这
is gonna be turned into a test that will
将变成一个测试，将
then call our actual REST API at four
然后在四点调用我们的实际REST API
slash reservations using an HTTP GET and
使用HTTP GET和
it's going to result in a response it
它会导致回应
comes back whose status should be status
返回其状态应为状态
code 200 and his constant type should be
代码200及其常量类型应为
application Jason utf-8 value and whose
应用程序Jason utf-8值及其
body should structurally match this we
身体在结构上应该与此匹配
should have a JSON with two objects to
应该具有两个对象的JSON
record two records in him and one has an
在他身上记录两张记录，其中一张有
idea of one the other an ID of two and
彼此的想法是两个ID
the first reservation should be Jane and
首先要预约的是简和
the second should be John and so on and
第二个应该是约翰，依此类推，
now in order for that to work we need to
现在，为了使它起作用，我们需要
set up that base information we need to
设置我们需要的基本信息
set up that Mach information right
正确设置马赫信息
because just before in our mock MVC or
因为就在我们的模拟MVC之前
mock web test client code here we used
我们在这里使用模拟网络测试客户端代码
mockito
模仿
and mock bean to tell spring to create a
和模拟 bean 告诉Spring创建一个
dummy set of data whenever somebody
每当有人的时候，虚拟的数据集
calls the reservation repository well we
很好地调用了预订存储库
need to do the same thing for this
为此需要做同样的事情
contract and the condo the compiler
合同和公寓编译器
plugin though our build plugin is gonna
插件，尽管我们的构建插件会
need to know from what base class our
需要知道我们来自什么基类
contract can extend to to inherit this
合同可以延伸到继承
set up logic okay and we need to provide
设置逻辑好，我们需要提供
that so let's create that base class
因此，让我们创建该基类
here and the base class looks all
在这里，基类看起来全部
together very familiar if you've used
在一起很熟悉，如果您曾经使用过
you know since we just did this on the
你知道，因为我们只是在
on the other side the base class is
另一方面，基类是
going to just be a thing with the the
只会与
mockito bit and one last bit of
模仿位和最后一位
initialization for our rest assured api
放心的api的初始化
this is the under this is the api that
这是根据这是API
underpin spring type contracts engine so
支撑Spring 式合约发动机
we need to do a little bit of setup just
我们需要做一些设置
for that which is i confess a little
对于那是我承认的一点
weird but
奇怪但是
you know it works so who cares so server
你知道它有用，所以谁在乎服务器
dot port equals zero and tell it to run
点端口等于零并告诉它运行
and we're gonna tell this local
我们要告诉这个当地人
application to run this on random port
应用程序在随机端口上运行
let's say we want to run on web
假设我们要在网络上运行
environment equals web environment dot
环境等于Web环境点
random port we want the base class to
我们想要基类的随机端口
run with spring runner dot class I'm
我参加了 Spring 跑步者圆点课程
gonna import um our configuration on
要导入我们的配置
Mike so it just as before reservation
迈克（Mike）就像预约之前一样
rest configuration there is this and
其余配置有这个
since it's going to run on a random port
因为它将在随机端口上运行
I want to inject that port and then take
我想注入那个端口然后取
advantage of that I'm gonna use the mock
优点是我要使用模拟
bean to inject our reservation
bean 注入我们的保留
repository alright and we'll say before
好的仓库，我们先说
public void set up throws exception ok
公共无效设置引发异常
and now mockito dot win this dot
现在mockito点赢得了这个点
reservation will post writ find all then
保留将发布令状，然后查找所有
return flux just new reservation no
返回流量只是新的保留
extra one we want some data here John
额外的一个，我们想要一些数据约翰
Jane and new reservation to John right
简和对约翰的新保留权
and then finally some set up for rest
然后终于要休息了
assured itself which we need to do in
放心，我们需要做的
this code base URI equals HTTP localhost
此代码库URI等于HTTP localhost
and the port of course is just that port
当然港口就是那个港口
all right so there's our updated code
好的，所以有我们的更新代码
it's like you know updated to reflect
就像您知道已更新以反映
the the new reality here our built
我们建造的新现实
plugin knows about this base class we've
插件知道我们已经拥有的这个基类
configured as much here so we said Kong
在这里配置了很多，所以我们说孔
example producer base class and because
示例生产者基类，因为
this is reactive we have this thing
这是反应性的，我们有这个东西
called test mode explicit now if you
如果您现在将测试模式显式调用
didn't have this it would try and do
没有这个，它将尝试做
mock NB C style testing but now it's an
模拟NB C样式测试，但现在
it's doing more reactive aware testing
它正在进行更具反应性的测试
as it's aware of the fact that this web
因为它知道这个网站
in
在
using the reactive spring web flex web
使用反应性Spring 腹板挠性腹板
runtime as opposed to just bringing me
运行时而不是仅仅带我
sea-based servlet runtime okay okay
基于海的servlet运行时好吧好吧
let's go see if that works
我们去看看是否可行
let's see if that works we can only we
让我们看看是否可行，我们只能
can find that out by going to our
可以通过访问我们的网站找到答案
producer maven clean
生产者行家清洁
packaging runs just try installing
打包运行只是尝试安装
all right good that worked we can prove
行之有效的好东西，我们可以证明
the negative of course by making this
负面的当然是通过这样做
Janet for example try moving clean
例如珍妮特（Janet）
stalling that I gained
我得到的拖延
you can see it broke and the thing that
你可以看到它坏了，
broke is this contract verified test
这份合同是否已通过测试
which is emitted for us it's a creative
对我们来说这是一个创意
force by the plugin and the contract
由插件和合同强制
verifier test of course looks like this
验证程序测试当然是这样的
it's like that so it's a bait it's a
就是这样，这是一个诱饵，这是一个
test that extends base class and it's
测试扩展了基类，它是
using rest-assured to make a request
使用放心的请求
that pokes at our reservations endpoint
戳我们的预订端点
is search the content type is to under
正在搜索内容类型为
the application adjacent looks like that
相邻的应用程序看起来像
the body looks like that and then the
身体看起来像那样，然后
name of the string reservation name is
字符串保留名称的名称是
equal to jannat in this case we know
在这种情况下等于詹娜特
that's not going to work so we go back
那是行不通的，所以我们回去
and fix it and the build should be green
并修复它，构建应该是绿色的
again until mave install and the reason
再次，直到mave install及其原因
I'm installing this the reason I'm
我安装这个的原因是
running this from the command line I'm
从命令行运行此
installing this is because I want to I
安装这是因为我要
want to if the build is successful I
想建立是否成功
want to deploy the resulting stubs of
想要部署的存根
our mock stubs into my local maven
我们的模拟存根进入我的本地专家
repository or in more reasonable
存储库或更合理
environment I would do a git push and
环境我会做一个git push和
then in the continuous integration
然后在持续整合中
environment this would result in a you
环境会导致你
know I'd run all the tests and if
知道我会进行所有测试，如果
they're all green I would do maven
他们都是绿色的，我会做专家
deploy and that would go to my
部署，这将归我
artifactory or my nexus or whatever and
人为因素或我的联系或其他任何因素
that would be the shared sort of well
那将是很好的共享
forgive me nexus between the consumer
原谅我与消费者之间的联系
and the producer they'd share artifacts
和他们将分享人工制品的生产者
they're the artifacts that they would
他们是他们会想要的文物
share in this case are the stubs so you
分享在这种情况下是存根，所以你
see we've got the jar which got
看到我们有罐子
installed per normal
按正常安装
we got the palm that XML again very
我们再次非常重视XML
normal we've got the stubs that's the
正常情况下，我们的存根是
interesting bit here that stub is just
有趣的是，存根只是
enough you know configuration for our
您足够了解我们的配置
client to now start up a web application
客户现在启动Web应用程序
using wire mock that looks suspiciously
使用看起来可疑的电线模拟
suspiciously like the API that we've
可疑地喜欢我们已经拥有的API
just built so let's go back to our our
刚刚建成，让我们回到我们的
client or consumer now and clean this
客户或消费者现在就清理它
code up we can actually just delete
代码，我们实际上可以删除
stuff which is my favorite kind of
我最喜欢的东西
coding okay so good bye and then instead
编码好再见，然后代替
of using wire mock explicitly we're
明确使用电线模拟的过程
going to use a stub runner so Auto
将要使用存根运行器，所以自动
configure stub winner and here and use
配置存根赢家并在此处使用
the com example artifact it's our group
com示例工件是我们的小组
ID and the producer
ID和生产者
artifact head you're gonna use the
您将要使用的神器头
latest version Ryan that makes sense
有意义的最新版本Ryan
because we want to use the latest
因为我们想使用最新的
version that has been deployed every
每次部署的版本
time you do get push on the producer
你确实会推动制作人
where the contracts are that's gonna get
合同在哪里
deployed into an artifact or an
部署到工件或
environment and presumably hopefully
环境，大概是希望
knock on wood that will also result in a
敲木头也将导致
build that gets pushed into production
被推入生产的建筑
and so what we want from the client
所以我们要从客户那里得到什么
perspective assuming this is a different
假设这是不同的观点
team working in a different space what
团队在不同的空间工作
we want is to pull down using this
我们要使用的是下拉
runtime sort of IV maven dependency
IV Maven依赖项的运行时排序
resolver thing what we want to do is
解析器要做的是
pull down the latest version of that
下拉那个的最新版本
stub which corresponds to the code
与代码相对应的存根
that's in production why would we want
这就是生产中为什么我们要
to test our client with anything less
用更少的东西来测试我们的客户
than the latest and greatest version of
比最新和最伟大的版本
the code which of course is the thing
代码当然是东西
that if this work if this client were
如果这个工作，如果这个客户是
deployed to production it would have to
部署到生产它将不得不
contend with so I'm gonna say pull down
与之抗衡，所以我要说下拉
the producer artifacts stubs pull down
生产者工件存根下拉
the latest version that's where the plus
这是最新版本
sign is and then finally start the
标志是，然后终于开始
resulting yr mock application on port
在端口上生成的yr模拟应用程序
8080 just as we did with the wire mock
8080就像我们使用线模拟一样
explicitly we could tell this app this
明确地，我们可以告诉这个应用程序
is you know we're using maven in the
您知道我们在使用Maven吗
java code here so to speak or maven
Java代码在这里可以这么说或行家
we're downloading the dependencies as
我们正在将依赖项下载为
though we were maven and so we have to
虽然我们是行家，所以我们必须
tell it where to find the stubs one way
告诉它在哪里可以找到存根
is to look on the classpath to look in
是看在类路径上看
the local m2 repository which is what I
我当地的M2资料库
want to do in this case or look an
想在这种情况下做或看起来
artifact err look in the configure
神器错误查看配置
artifacts or artifact repository for
的工件或工件存储库
your environment but I'm going to look
您的环境，但我要看一下
in local and you know home in two
在当地，你知道家里有两个
repositories I'm gonna say local um and
我要说的是本地存储库
with that there I think we're okay I
在那里，我认为我们还可以
think actually everything else stays the
认为实际上其他一切仍然存在
way it is the client doesn't need to
客户端不需要的方式
change all we have to do is get rid of
改变我们要做的就是摆脱
the goofy wire mock code there since
自那以来的愚蠢电线模拟代码
that's now gonna be trapped transitively
现在将被暂时转移
resolved and we can restart
解决，我们可以重新启动
okay what did we do wrong well I think
好吧，我认为我们做错了什么
we just found the bug huh look at that
我们刚刚发现了这个错误，呵呵
it's expecting a reservation whose ID is
期望ID为的预订
one and name is equal to null null
一个且名称等于null null
pointer right so clearly that didn't
指针非常清楚，没有
work
工作
name isn't a thing that's coming across
名字不是偶然的事情
the wire and we can confirm as much by
电汇，我们可以通过
seeing that it says that reservation
看到它说那个保留
name is equal to Jane not name so that
名字等于简而不是名字
catches the incompatibility that catches
捕捉到的不兼容
the fat fingering between the client and
客户与
the service that would have otherwise
否则会有的服务
doomed our application in production so
注定了我们在生产中的应用，因此
let's refactor the code a little bit
让我们重构一下代码
here do we factor great compile just
我们在这里考虑很好的编译只是
make sure everything's happy again and
确保一切再次开心，
if that's okay we'll restart this test
如果可以的话，我们将重新开始测试
good
好
okay now that's still broken why is that
好吧，现在还是坏了，为什么
we're expecting reservation name was our
我们期望预订名称是我们的
contract say Jane and John
合同上说简和约翰
so
所以
how curious
多么好奇
so there's our client code calm example
所以有我们的客户代码平静的例子
producer 8080 we want to confirm that
生产者8080我们要确认
when we call get all the reservations
当我们打电话给所有预订
that let's see
那让我们看看
that installed right calm example
安装正确的冷静的例子
producer great
制片人很棒
the quest received
收到的任务
did I miss something obvious here
我想念这里明显的东西吗
auto-configure step manner calm example
自动配置步进方式平静示例
producer I tease stubs mode Springwood
制片人我挑逗存根模式斯普林伍德
test
测试
change and John
变化和约翰
do I have some weirdness
我有些奇怪吗
how bizarre if we go here it's very
如果我们去这里真是太奇怪了
clearly returning those two records so
显然返回了这两个记录，所以
in this case I wonder if I can just
在这种情况下，我想知道是否可以
there's some goofiness with my
我有些傻
repository perhaps calm example may even
仓库也许平静的例子甚至
clean install and the producer side it
干净的安装和生产方
very clearly says rossette reservations
很明显说玫瑰红预订
Content ID one reservation name is Jane
内容ID的一个预订名称是Jane
and then John that's oh that's why it's
然后是约翰，这就是为什么
not valid it's not a valid JSON array
无效，它不是有效的JSON数组
right so that's oh that's interesting
对，所以这很有趣
I don't know if that has anything to do
不知道有什么事吗
with it so let's try that again
有了它，让我们再试一次
clean that up middle clean install
清理中间清理安装
I should have used the object literal
我应该使用对象字面量
syntax clearly here I get all fancy
语法在这里我很喜欢
reasonably sure this is the issue okay
有理由确定这是问题
that works
这样可行
now if we go back to the client one more
现在，如果我们再回到客户那里
time
时间
all right good so that fixed it so the
好的，这样就解决了
issue was that I was I wasn't sending
问题是我当时没有发送
valid I was sending one record back not
有效，我发回的记录不是
to and so I'm that didn't match and
到，所以我那不匹配，
that's the that's the point right we
那就是我们要说的重点
want to make sure these things match so
想确保这些东西匹配
there we go there we have written a
那里我们去那里我们写了一个
spring cut contract definition that can
Spring 合同的定义可以
test against our reactive web endpoint
针对我们的反应式网络端点进行测试
we can ensure the integrity of the
我们可以确保
client and the service we have ensured
客户和我们确保的服务
that the the the system works and we can
该系统工作正常，我们可以
now you know decouple these things
现在你知道这些东西脱钩了
obviously if you're not using the you
显然，如果您不使用
know spring cut contract for the test
知道测试的 Spring 合同
and the client maybe you're doing an
客户可能正在做一个
iPhone development around html5 or
iPhone开发围绕html5或
something you can use for example the
您可以使用的东西，例如
spring cloud contract stuff right a jar
spring-cloud-contract的东西一罐
like this and you can run it using a
这样，您可以使用
script like that and that's script that
那样的脚本，那个脚本
script says okay I'm gonna run this jar
脚本说好，我要运行这个罐子
passing in the work offline attributes
传递工作离线属性
stuff mode equals local and I want to
填充模式等于本地，我想
run this calm example let's say in this
运行这个平静的例子，让我们在这说
case would be producer plus 8080 so
情况将是生产者加8080，所以
let's update that file Emacs and I would
让我们更新该文件Emacs，我会
say producer okay and do it and that's
说制片人还可以，那就是
gonna spin up an API here it's a fake
会旋转一个API，这是假的
API oops
API oops
oh okay I have a sinking suspicion this
哦，好吧，我对此深有怀疑
one is related to my choice of JDK so
一个与我对JDK的选择有关
you're just thinking SDK this Java SDK
您只是在想SDK这个Java SDK
use Java 8 for now and then we try it
现在使用Java 8，然后尝试
again not sure why that would work but I
再次不确定为什么会这样，但是我
have a sinking suspicion that's what it
对此有怀疑
is so it's important in 83
所以在83年很重要
there's our API alright so it was choice
有我们的API，所以选择
of it was I'm using Java 11 by default
其中是我默认使用Java 11
it I think I might have an older version
我想我可能有旧版本
of the stubborn urge our API either way
顽固地敦促我们的API
but running on Java it works just fine
但是在Java上运行就可以了
and so that should get you to where you
所以那应该带你到你的地方
want to go and of course if you'd seen
想去，当然，如果你看到了
the previous video you know that this is
上一个视频，您知道这是
a the string Club contract is you know
字符串俱乐部合同是吗
far and away more interesting than when
比何时更有趣
I've shown here it can actually be used
我在这里展示了它实际上可以使用
to support messaging you know I'll be up
支持消息，你知道我会起来的
with Kafka or something like that it can
用Kafka或类似的东西
be used to to to stub out service
习惯于存根服务
registry and they don't through the
注册表，他们不通过
discovery clean abstraction so you know
发现干净的抽象，所以你知道
you can do a lot of things here beyond
您可以在这里做很多事情
just REST API is but it's an interesting
只是REST API，但这很有趣
approach and it helps ensure that that
方法，它有助于确保
both producer and consumer match and
生产者和消费者都匹配并且
that you don't have to stand up a full
你不必站得满满的
replication or in a reproduction of the
复制或复制
whole production system just to be able
整个生产系统只是为了能够
to test as though you were in production
测试好像您正在生产中
with that my friends thanks so much for
我的朋友非常感谢
watching and we'll see you next time
看，下次见
you
您